http://www.uac.edu.au/about/privacy-legal

QAS Check & Change
Institution Hub (member login)
Search
Close
Popular searches
Course search
Educational Access Schemes (EAS)
Admission criteria
ATAR
Schools Recommendations Schemes (SRS)
UAC disclaimer
By visiting and using the information on this website you agree to the following:
In the preparation of these web pages, every effort has been made to offer the most current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nonetheless, inadvertent errors can occur, and applicable laws, rules and procedures often change. The Universities Admissions Centre (NSW & ACT)(UAC) does not warrant or represent that this site is free from errors or omissions or that the information contained therein is suitable for your intended use.
Information is provided to UAC by the institutions. The institutions may amend details without notice and for any reason in response to changing circumstances. The institutions reserve the right to change any unit of study, or withdraw any unit or course of study, or impose limitations on enrolments in any unit or course of study.
You accept all risks and responsibility for losses, damages, costs and other consequences resulting directly or indirectly from using this site and any information or material available from it.
To the maximum extent permitted by law, UAC excludes all liability for any loss or damage (including without limitation, any special or consequential loss or damage) to any person arising directly or indirectly out of the use or inability to use this site and any information or material available from it.
COPYRIGHT
UAC and individual contributing institutions are the owners of the copyright in UAC publications and material on UAC’s website.
Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study, criticism or review, or otherwise as permitted under the Copyright Act 1968, no part may be reproduced by any process without UAC’s written permission. Enquiries should be in writing and addressed to the Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
UAC has no objection to secondary schools and UAC’s participating tertiary institutions reproducing the publication in full provided it is for use only within their own institution, and this copyright statement is included.
If the document isn’t reproduced in full, sections should not be copied out of context where information could be incomplete and/or misleading. Secondary schools and UAC’s participating tertiary institutions must ensure that this information isn’t transmitted to any other person or body without prior permission from UAC.
LINKS
Links connecting this site with other sites are for convenience only and their presence does not mean that UAC endorses or approves those sites, their content or the people who manage them.
TIMES
Times indicated on this website are stated as Sydney time.
ADVERTISING DISCLAIMER
UAC does not necessarily endorse any product or service that may be advertised on this website.
UAC accessibility statement
If you have a disability and are having problems with the UAC application process, contact us. You can call us on 1300 275 822 – from mobiles on (02) 9752 0200 or from overseas on +61 2 9752 0200 – between 8.30am and 4.30pm (Sydney time.) Monday to Friday, email us using the enquiry form or write to the Equity Unit, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128, Australia. We will help you with your application.
UAC works within the principles of usability and universal design to deliver accessible web content for all users, including people with disabilities. Our website aims to comply with best practices and standards as defined by Section 508 of the U.S. Rehabilitation Act and the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) of the World Wide Web Consortium Web Accessibility Initiative (W3C WAI). These guidelines explain how to make web content more accessible for people with disabilities, and incorporate three levels of accessibility conformance (A, AA and AAA). The UAC website aims to meet Level AA.
WE VALUE YOUR OPINION
If you have questions about this accessibility statement, or suggestions for improvements to UAC’s website, applications and services, please get in touch.
You can contact us in the following ways:
Call us on 1300 275 822 between 8.30am and 4.30pm (Sydney time) Monday to Friday.Use our enquiry form.Write to us at Equity Unit, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128, Australia.
Applicants' responsibilities
YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES AS AN APPLICANT
When you apply through UAC, you have certain responsibilities.
By meeting your responsibilities you'll ensure that your application will be processed and assessed as soon as possible.
You must:
read the instructions before submitting your applicationread the relevant parts of the UAC Guide, other publications or corresponding information on this websitefollow any institution-specific instructionsprovide true and complete information in connection with your applicationprovide true and complete copies of official documentation with your application where requestedaccept the conditions set out in the declaration.IF YOU FAIL TO MEET YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES
UAC may cancel your application and/or institutions may withdraw any place offered if at any stage you have submitted an application that contains information that UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete. For further information read the policy statement below on untrue or incomplete information submitted by applicants.
POLICY STATEMENT ON UNTRUE OR INCOMPLETE INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY APPLICANTS
UAC recognises that all decisions which affect an applicant must be made fairly using appropriate academic or other criteria as specified by the participating institutions.
Selection into courses by application to UAC is based on merit. It is the responsibility of applicants to ensure that they comply with all instructions when submitting a UAC application. The responsibilities of applicants are set out above.
An application must be complete and correct and all attempts at academic study must be disclosed. Applicants must accept the conditions set out in the declaration and authority when they apply.
UAC will review, and may take action against, anyone who submits an application that contains information that UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete. That application may also be cancelled.
UAC will also investigate, and may take action against, an applicant who, by any other means, has or could have achieved an advantage over other applicants.
Examples of conduct by an applicant which will be investigated by UAC include, but are not limited to:
submitting an incomplete or falsified academic transcriptfailing to declare previous study at secondary, post-secondary or tertiary levelsubmitting an incorrect or otherwise misleading statement of employment experienceclaiming special consideration of educational disadvantage based on incorrect informationhaving some other person complete a selection task on the applicant's behalf such as an interview, audition or a portfolio of workclaiming membership of a special selection group when not a member of that group.The procedures for processing applications suspected of being in some way incomplete or untrue have been approved by the NSW Vice-Chancellors' Committee.
These procedures accept the right of applicants to be treated fairly and without prejudice, and in accordance with the principles of natural justice.
UAC privacy policy
When you apply to the Universities Admissions Centre (NSW & ACT) (UAC) you provide a lot of personal information, sometimes including health information.
UAC values the privacy of your personal information and recognises the importance of protecting it. UAC is bound by the following legislation:
Privacy and Personal Information Protection Act 1998 (NSW)Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)Health Records and Information Privacy Act 2002 (NSW).This means that UAC must uphold the NSW State Information Protection Principles, the Australian Privacy Principles and the NSW Health Privacy Principles. UAC is committed to upholding these principles and has implemented policies and procedures to ensure they are met.
ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy sets out how and what information is collected, maintained and disclosed (including identification of individuals) for the services UAC provides in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
If you do not agree to any of the provisions of this Policy, you should not use UAC’s website or services, lodge a UAC application or provide UAC with any personal information. By visiting the UAC website, applying, using any of our services or providing us with your information, you agree to the information being collected, held, used and disclosed as set out in this Privacy Policy.
SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This policy applies to all methods of collecting personal and sensitive information (via hardcopy, electronic or verbal means) including but not limited to the following:
online UAC applications and serviceschanges to personal detailsreceipt of educational resultscalculation of the ATAR, if necessaryadditional documentation provided by you as part of your application/selectronic information provided as part of your application/sinformation provided by third parties on behalf of yousurveys you may completedraws or competitions you may enterdigital images captured for applicant identification purposesexam and tertiary studies results from relevant institutions.WHAT INFORMATION DOES UAC COLLECT?
The type of personal information UAC collects includes:
your contact details (including name, address, telephone number, email address)your date of birthyour genderyour citizenship detailsyour language spoken at homeyour country of birthyour year of arrival in Australia (if relevant)your educational achievementsyour professional qualificationsinformation related to any disability you may haveinformation related to your health or the health of a family memberinformation about the highest educational attainment of your parent/sdetails of your proficiency in Englishyour HSC and other examination resultsyour Australian Tertiary Admission Rank (ATAR)your course preferencesyour status as an Aboriginal or Torres Strait Islanderpayment details for goods and services provided.UAC will only collect information for lawful purposes related to its function.
If we receive unsolicited personal information, as soon as reasonably possible we determine if we could have collected the personal information under the Australian Privacy Principles.
If we consider we could have collected the personal information, we will retain it as if we had collected it under the Australian Privacy Principles.If we consider we could not have collected the personal information, we will (if it is lawful and reasonable to do so) destroy the information or ensure the information is de-identified.UAC provides your personal information and, where applicable, sensitive information, to all institutions to which you have applied. If you do not provide personal or sensitive information where required, UAC may not be able to process your application. Please contact UAC’s Privacy Officer if you have any queries.
If you would like further information about, or clarification of, the information handling practices at UAC or require more detail than this document provides, please contact the Privacy Officer at:Privacy Officer UAC Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128 Phone: +61 2 9752 0200 Email: privacy@uac.edu.au
HOW DOES UAC COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION?
Online applications
UAC collects personal information and, in some circumstances, information regarding your health, or information about someone else, to process your application for admission to tertiary institutions. Only information that is necessary to fulfil the functions and activities of UAC will be collected. Such collection will be by lawful and fair means and will not be unreasonably intrusive.
Sensitive and health information will only be collected if it is directly related to the primary purpose for which the information will be collected or as required by law or with the specific and informed consent of the individual.
Where practicable, UAC will collect personal or sensitive information direct from the individual. In some cases, UAC may collect information from a third party, such as another educational institution, other interstate tertiary admission centres or a government authority. UAC may also collect personal or sensitive information from others that you have authorised to act on your behalf, such as a health practitioner, an employment agency, a former employer or a contractor.
In providing the details of your authorised person or agency to UAC you are consenting to the collection of your personal and sensitive information from your authorised person or agency.
Generally, you will be aware we have collected personal information or have authorised collection of personal information from third parties or be aware that we are obtaining information from them.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (‘Google’). Google Analytics uses ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for website operators and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Logged-in user, demographic and interest reporting
UAC uses a specific cookie to facilitate the use of Google Universal Analytics for users logged in to UAC or UAC applications. If you are logged in, UAC may use a unique ID in combination with Google Analytics to track and analyse pages you view and services you use. This unique ID is distinct from your UAC user ID. UAC will not upload any data that allows Google to personally identify an individual (such as names, government reference numbers, email addresses, or any similar data), or data that permanently identifies a device (such as a mobile phone’s unique device identifier if such an identifier cannot be reset).
UAC has also implemented Demographics and Interest Reporting from the Google Analytics Advertising Features. UAC will use this data to improve and expand information and services through a better understanding of visitors to our website and how they use our website. Visitors can opt out of Google’s interest-based ads or edit the interests and demographics associated with their Google Account by changing Ad settings.
Want to block tracking?
Visitors can also block tracking by Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, available for all common browsers.
Google Ads and Google Marketing Platform
We use Google Ads and Google Marketing Platform to advertise UAC across a variety of third-party websites and measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. Google Ads or Google Marketing Platform remarketing may serve ads to you based on your interactions with this and other websites by placing a cookie on your machine. For example, we may advertise to previous visitors to our site who haven't completed an application. This cookie does not allow us to gather personal information or provide a means to identify you. The data gathered is anonymous. We also share this information with our trusted advertising and analytics partners.
Want to opt out?
If you want to opt out of seeing personalised ads served by Google, you can change Ad Settings.
Facebook
We use Facebook pixels to advertise UAC on Facebook. This cookie provides us with data about ads served to users on Facebook who later visited our website. We also use this information to measure the effectiveness of marketing campaigns and to target ads to you based on your previous behaviour. For example, we may show you an ad if you came to our site but did not complete an application.
You can opt-out of Facebook’s use of cookies and Facebook Pixel Re-marketing through settings on your Facebook Account.
This feature does not affect this Privacy Policy as it applies to applicants.
Other platforms
We also use the following platforms to collect data:
Google Marketing PlatformHotjarMonsidoCampaign MonitorSurveyMonkeyLinkedInTwitterInTouchInstagramSnapchatYouTube.WEBSITE SERVERUAC uses website server and error logs to record and analyse activity on our website and services, provide stable online resources and improve the services that UAC and institutions provide. These logs also allow us to detect and prevent fraud and unauthorised access to our systems. All server requests are logged and information captured by this process may include:
IP addresssession timestampsgeolocationbrowser typeoperating systemreferralsresources usederror data.Data is encrypted and securely stored and access to the data is restricted under strict protocols. Log data may also be shared with higher education institutions to enable them to measure activity on offered courses.
WHY DOES UAC COLLECT THIS DATA?
For online applications, UAC collects the personal and sensitive information necessary for us to provide you with the services you have requested from us, and to manage your UAC application.
Other data is collected by the tools described above to support our mission as follows:
measure how our websites, services and tools are used so we can continually deliver better user experiencesevaluate the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and deliver targeted, useful advertisingseek feedback from customers and stakeholderscommunicate important information via all popular digital platforms to provide free and timely advice.HOW DOES UAC HOLD THIS INFORMATION?
Your personal information is held in secure archive databases at UAC and an Australian-owned data centre. It is protected under the relevant privacy legislation as described above.
Arrangements with our provider requires personal information we collect to be stored on a server in Australia only and for our provider/s to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles with respect to that personal information.
We have also requested any overseas recipient of information to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles as if they were an entity bound by them.
If you are a current NSW Higher School Certificate student, your Year 12 results will be held along with Year 12 results from other states and territories in Australia in secure archive databases at UAC and an Australian-owned data centre. If you are eligible for an Australian Tertiary Admission Rank (ATAR) or a Limited ATAR, these will also be held in the databases.
Your results, including your ATAR if you are eligible, will also be held on similar archives at tertiary admissions centres in other states in Australia. Results held on these archives will only be accessed by the relevant tertiary admission centre if you apply for tertiary study through that centre, or directly with an institution participating in that centre.
For any payments you make via our websites, over the telephone or face to face, we use a recognised payment service provider that is required to take reasonable steps to protect your information. We also take reasonable precautions to ensure that any information you provide to us through our websites is transferred and treated securely.
HOW DOES UAC USE THIS INFORMATION?
UAC uses this information to process applications for admission to tertiary education institutions. This includes providing universities, other tertiary institutions and tertiary admission centres elsewhere in Australia with the information that you provide to us. UAC may also disclose this information to the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, and other agencies as described in UAC’s declaration and authority as lawfully required or where UAC reasonably considers it necessary to make such disclosure.
WHAT ABOUT THIRD PARTIES?
To perform certain business functions, UAC may contract the services of third parties, such as printing specialists.
In these circumstances, where necessary, some of your information may be shared with these third parties for the express purpose of undertaking the specified service and for no other purpose. These contractors are bound by the same Australian Privacy Principles as UAC.
Your information may also be shared with any authorised representative/s that you have nominated, and with any organisations with which we are required by law to share the information.
UAC does not buy or sell mailing lists.
MY UAC: Android version
The Android version of My UAC uses the Google Maps API facility. The Google Maps service is made available to you under licence from Google Inc. By using the Google Maps service and any material accessed from Google Maps, you also agree to be bound by:
the Google Terms of Servicethe Google Privacy Policy.Google Cloud Vision
UAC may provide applicant data to Google Cloud Vision for the purpose of computer vision of documents uploaded to your application to decrease your application processing time.
DECLARATION
When applying, you'll be asked to accept a declaration which outlines what UAC does with your personal information in the application process.
HOW DO I ACCESS MY INFORMATION?
Under the Australian Privacy Principles, you are generally entitled to access the information UAC holds about you, but we will require proof of identity – and some requests can be refused. The time it takes to respond to your request depends on the type of information you require, and a fee may be charged.
You may be able to access some personal information on UAC's website or mobile apps using your UAC application number and UAC PIN. No personal information is posted on the internet.
WHAT DO I DO IF THE INFORMATION UAC HOLDS ABOUT ME IS INCORRECT?
Please tell us. We want our records to be accurate, complete and up to date. Unless we disagree with you about the accuracy or completeness of a record, we will generally correct it upon request, or suggest alternative arrangements for updating our records.
WHAT DO I DO ABOUT BREACH OF PRIVACY?
To make a complaint about an alleged breach of your privacy, write to The Privacy Officer, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128 and explain what has happened.
If possible, include the name/s and position/s of staff at UAC or at the institution/s who have contacted you. Include your UAC application number and copies of any correspondence that illustrates your problem.
The Privacy Officer will ensure that your concerns are investigated and will write to you as soon as possible. Your application will not be jeopardised in any way.
HOW CAN I CONTACT UAC ABOUT A PRIVACY ISSUE?
Contact the Privacy Officer:Privacy Officer UAC Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128 Phone: +61 2 9752 0200 Email: privacy@uac.edu.au
If you have a general enquiry about UAC or your application, contact UAC.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
UAC reserves the right to review and amend this policy from time to time and to notify you by posting an updated version on this website.
HOW DO I FIND OUT MORE?
For more information about privacy and the Australian Privacy Principles, visit the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.
Updated March 2020
UAC copyright notice
UAC and individual contributing institutions are the owners of the copyright in UAC publications and material on UAC’s website.
Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study, criticism or review, or otherwise as permitted under the Copyright Act 1968, no part may be reproduced by any process without UAC’s written permission. Enquiries should be in writing and addressed to The Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
UAC has no objection to secondary schools and UAC’s participating tertiary institutions reproducing the publication in full provided it is for use only within their own institution, and this copyright statement is included.
If the document isn’t reproduced in full, sections should not be copied out of context where information could be incomplete and/or misleading. Secondary schools and UAC’s participating tertiary institutions must ensure that this information isn’t transmitted to any other person or body without prior permission from UAC.
UAC social media guidelines
FACEBOOK
UAC's Facebook page allows users to stay informed and ask questions about the application and admissions process.
If you have a question or request, give us as much detail about it as you can. This will help us to understand your situation and to provide the most helpful, relevant advice. For privacy reasons we cannot give advice about your application using Facebook. If you have questions about your individual circumstances, use our enquiry form or call us between 8.30am and 4.30pm Monday to Friday (Sydney time) on 1300 275 822 (from mobiles on (02) 9752 0200).
We will usually respond to posts on weekdays (except public holidays) between 8.30am and 4.30pm Sydney time. At busy times of the year these hours may be extended. We answer questions as quickly as we can, but we may sometimes need to ask for more details by email or phone.
Keep the tone of your Facebook posts positive and constructive.
Things that don't belong on UAC's Facebook page include:
content that is defamatory, threatening, harassing, abusive, libellous, unlawful, obscene, hateful or embarrassing as determined by UACinappropriate or illegal content: UAC will delete posts with profane, racist, sexist, abusive, threatening, defamatory, illegal or obscene content. Posts linking to any online content that would violate these guidelines will also be deletedcontent that infringes on the rights of anyone else, including intellectual property, privacy or publicity rights.People need to feel comfortable about posting on UAC's Facebook page. Please abide by Facebook's Community Standards. Treat others with consideration and don't post or respond to inflammatory messages.
We welcome your feedback on our Facebook page and are always working to improve it.
YOUTUBE
UAC's YouTube channel provides instructional videos to help applicants, school and institution staff and the public.
Comments, suggestions or questions about any of these videos can be made by posting on our Facebook page or contacting us.
By using UAC's YouTube channel you:
understand that UAC's videos may not be embedded on any third-party platform or website unless written permission has been granted by UAC, and that UAC does not authorise or endorse video responses to any of its videosagree to abide by YouTube's Community Guidelines. If you don't, UAC will report your behaviour, which may result in the termination of your accountunderstand that UAC retains and asserts all moral and exclusive rights of ownership of intellectual property, granted by law in Australia and internationally, for the protection of its video content. Infringement of these rights may result in legal actionunderstand that UAC does not guarantee the accuracy or usefulness of any of its video content. You agree to waive any legal rights to the extent permitted by law and indemnify UAC against all claims and liability for damages, costs and expenses resulting from any interaction with video content owned by UAC.We welcome your feedback on our service and are always working to improve it.
TWITTER
UAC's Twitter account provides an information service allowing followers to stay informed and ask questions about the application and admissions process.
If you have a question or request, give us as much detail about it as you can. This will help us to understand your situation and provide the most helpful, relevant advice. For privacy reasons we cannot give advice about specific applications using Twitter. If you have questions about your individual circumstances, use our enquiry form or call us between 8.30am and 4.30pm Monday to Friday (Sydney time) on 1300 275 822 (from mobiles on (02) 9752 0200).
We will usually respond to tweets on weekdays (except public holidays) between 8.30am and 4.30pm Sydney time. At busy times of the year these hours may be extended. We will try to answer your questions as quickly as we can, but we may sometimes need to ask for more details by email or phone.
Be positive and constructive with your tweets. Please don't harass other users. People need to feel comfortable when interacting with UAC's Twitter account. Abide by The Twitter Rules. If you don't, UAC may report your behaviour, which can result in the termination of your account.
The following are not acceptable and will be blocked or reported:
defamatory, threatening, harassing, abusive, libellous, unlawful, obscene, hateful or embarrassing tweets as determined by UACtweets that feature inappropriate or illegal content such as profane, racist, sexist, abusive, threatening, defamatory, illegal or obscene content.Treat others with consideration, and don't post or respond to inflammatory messages.
Do not impersonate UAC or its agents. If you do, you'll be reported to Twitter and your account may be terminated.
We welcome your feedback on our service and are always working to improve it.
QAS disclaimer
CURRENCY OF THE STATEMENT
The UAC Qualifications Assessment Statement is valid as at the date of issue. The statement is based on the common assessment procedures and guidelines approved by UAC's participating institutions as at the date of issue. These guidelines are set using research undertaken by UAC. This research involves recommendations from Australian Education International through the National Office of Overseas Skills Recognition (AEI-NOOSR), the National Academic Recognition Information Centre for the United Kingdom (UK NARIC) and other relevant sources available to UAC. These assessment procedures and guidelines, research and recommendations are confidential information of UAC or made available to UAC on a confidential basis. UAC and participating institutions reserve the right to change the level of comparison of qualifications as additional information becomes available.
PARTICIPATING INSTITUTIONS
The Qualifications Assessment Statement is issued to provide prospective UAC applicants with an assessment of their qualifications. This may be used as a guide by admissions officers in determining prospective applicants' eligibility for courses offered at UAC's participating institutions.
USE OF THE STATEMENT
The Qualifications Assessment Statement does not bind any institution to accept UAC's assessment.
Eligibility for course entry is determined by the institutions themselves.
The statement does not guarantee admission to an institution. There are a number of factors affecting entry into a course. Entry is based on competition as places may be limited and some courses may have additional requirements or prerequisites.
Qualifications may also be superseded by, or looked at in combination with, other assessable qualifications that you may hold.
For accurate advice on eligibility for course entry, please take your Qualifications Assessment Statement along with any other qualifications to the admissions office at the institution/s to which you are applying.
UAC RANKS
The UAC rank disclosed on your Qualifications Assessment Statement is a guide only. It is based on documentation provided for assessment and is subject to changes to the confidential common assessment procedures and guidelines. Participating institutions use UAC ranks in different ways when assessing applications for admission. Some institutions may apply different weightings to these UAC ranks as qualifications may be looked at in combination with other assessable qualifications you may hold, or may use these ranks in conjunction with other selection criteria. Other institutions may not use UAC ranks for qualifications that have been superseded by other qualifications you may have.
ACCEPTANCE OF QUALIFICATIONS
Participating institutions may not accept all qualifications as a basis of entry into courses. Contact the admissions offices at institutions for information about acceptance of qualifications.
REFUND POLICY
Please apply carefully as UAC will NOT refund fees and charges under any circumstances, except as required by law. You must keep a record of the date and time of your payment as proof of payment. All UAC fees and charges are in Australian dollars (AUD) and include 10% GST.
COPYRIGHT
UAC is the owner of the copyright in your statement. You may copy it to provide to a participating institution for the purpose of consideration of an application for admission or a proposed application for admission. No part may otherwise be reproduced by any process without UAC's written permission.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
UAC collects personal information and, in some circumstances, information regarding your health, or information about someone other than yourself, for the purpose of processing your application for admission to tertiary institutions.
If you are providing personal information about someone other than yourself, you should tell them about UAC's Privacy Policy.
While your personal information is generally collected from you, UAC also collects information about you from other educational institutions that you have attended.
UAC provides your personal information and, where applicable, your health information, all participating institutions. If you do not provide personal information where required in your application, UAC may not be able to process your application. For more information, read UAC's Privacy Policy. Please contact UAC's Privacy Officer if you have any queries.
You are able to gain access to any personal information and health information that is held about you by UAC. To obtain access, or if you have any questions, write to The Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
Workplace Health & Safety Guidelines
Guidelines for employees, contractors and visitors
Statement of Business Ethics
A guide for contractors, consultants, suppliers, tenderers and business partners
Whistleblower Policy
Policy for whistleblower rights and protections
UAC declarations
Undergraduate declaration
Your application cannot be considered unless you or the person you have authorised to act on your behalf accept all conditions set out below.
UAC collects information about you, including information you provide in this application, to assist in the assessment of your application. This information may be used as described below.
1. I declare that I have read and understand the questions and that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understand ‘Your responsibilities as an applicant’ and the ‘Policy statement on untrue or incomplete information submitted by applicants’ on this page.
3. I declare that I have read and understand the section ‘Collection of personal information’ below.
4. I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to obtain available official records from any educational institution attended by me. I understand that UAC is not responsible if any institution does not provide these records.
5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
7. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all institutions participating in undergraduate admissions through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions or affiliates.
8. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia, Universities Australia member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
9. I authorise any future educational institution I attend as a result of this application to provide all of my results from future studies to UAC or a person nominated by UAC. I authorise UAC or the nominated person to collect, receive, store, transfer and use all such information and all information in or connected with this application for research purposes. I give these authorities on condition that all information provided pursuant to them is deidentified by UAC or the nominated person.
10. I understand that UAC or a participating institution for which I have a preference may disclose the personal information I have given in this application to the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, for the purpose of:
use in connection with the Higher Education Information Management System (HEIMS) and/oruse in connection with the National Data Collection on University Applications and Offers and/orother collections as the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, may lawfully require from time to time.11. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an application or enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
12. I understand that UAC, on behalf of the participating institutions, makes offers based on the information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer.
13. I understand that UAC will release details of my course preferences and offers to my school/college and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish these details to be released to my school/college.
14. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
15. I understand that all fees paid to UAC in connection with my application are not refundable under any circumstances except as required by law.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
UAC collects personal information and, in some circumstances, information regarding your health, or information about someone other than yourself, for the purpose of processing your application for undergraduate admission to tertiary institutions.
If you are providing personal information about someone other than yourself, you should tell them about UAC's Privacy Policy.
While your personal information is generally collected from you, UAC also collects information about you from other educational institutions that you have attended.
UAC provides your personal information and, where applicable, your health information to all institutions participating in undergraduate admissions through UAC. If you do not provide personal information where required in your application, UAC will not be able to process your application. Contact UAC's Privacy Officer if you have any queries.
You are able to gain access to any personal information and health information that is held about you by UAC. To obtain access, or if you have any questions, write to:
The Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
For more information, read UAC's Privacy Policy.
International declaration
Your application cannot be considered unless you or the person you have authorised to act on your behalf accept all conditions set out below.
UAC collects information about you, including information you provide in this application, to assist in the assessment of your application. This information may be used as described below.
1. I declare that I have read and understand the questions and that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understand ‘Your responsibilities as an applicant’ and the ‘Policy statement on untrue or incomplete information submitted by applicants’ on this page.
3. I declare that I have read and understand the section ‘Collection of personal information’ below.
4. I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to obtain available official records from any educational institution attended by me. I understand that UAC is not responsible if any institution does not provide these records.
5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
7. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all institutions participating in international undergraduate admissions through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions or affiliates.
8. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia, Universities Australia member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
9. I authorise any future educational institution I attend as a result of this application to provide all of my results from future studies to UAC or a person nominated by UAC. I authorise UAC or the nominated person to collect, receive, store, transfer and use all such information and all information in or connected with this application for research purposes. I give these authorities on condition that all information provided pursuant to them is deidentified by UAC or the nominated person.
10. I understand that UAC or a participating institution for which I have a preference may disclose the personal information I have given in this application to the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, for the purpose of:
use in connection with the Higher Education Information Management System (HEIMS), and/oruse in connection with the National Data Collection on University Applications and Offers, and/orother collections as the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, may lawfully require from time to time.11. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an application or enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
12. I understand that UAC, on behalf of the participating institutions, makes offers based on the information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer.
13. I understand that UAC will release details of my course preferences and offers to my school/college and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish these details to be released to my school/college.
14. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
15. I understand that all fees paid to UAC in connection with my application are not refundable under any circumstances except as required by law.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
UAC collects personal information and, in some circumstances, information regarding your health, or information about someone other than yourself, for the purpose of processing your application for international undergraduate admission to tertiary institutions.
If you are providing personal information about someone other than yourself, you should tell them about UAC's Privacy Policy.
While your personal information is generally collected from you, UAC also collects information about you from other educational institutions that you have attended. UAC provides your personal information and, where applicable, your health information to all institutions participating in international undergraduate admissions through UAC. If you do not provide personal information where required in your application, UAC will not be able to process your application. Contact UAC's Privacy Officer if you have any queries.
You are able to gain access to any personal information and health information that is held about you by UAC. To obtain access, or if you have any questions, write to:
The Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
For more information, read UAC's Privacy Policy.
Postgraduate declaration
Your application cannot be considered unless you or the person you have authorised to act on your behalf accept all conditions set out below.
UAC collects information about you, including information you provide in this application, to assist in the assessment of your application. This information may be used as described below.
1. I declare that I have read and understand the questions and that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understand ‘Your responsibilities as an applicant’ and the ‘Policy statement on untrue or incomplete information submitted by applicants’ on this page.
3. I declare that I have read and understand the section ‘Collection of personal information’ below.
4. I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to obtain available official records from any educational institution attended by me. I understand that UAC is not responsible if any institution does not provide these records.
5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
7. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all institutions participating in postgraduate admissions through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions or affiliates.
8. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia, Universities Australia member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
9. I authorise any future educational institution I attend as a result of this application to provide all of my results from future studies to UAC or a person nominated by UAC. I authorise UAC or the nominated person to collect, receive, store, transfer and use all such information and all information in or connected with this application for research purposes. I give these authorities on condition that all information provided pursuant to them is deidentified by UAC or the nominated person.
10. I understand that UAC or a participating institution for which I have a preference may disclose the personal information I have given in this application to the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, for the purpose of:
use in connection with the Higher Education Information Management System (HEIMS), and/oruse in connection with the National Data Collection on University Applications and Offers, and/orother collections as the Department of Education, Skills and Employment, or its successor, may lawfully require from time to time.11. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an application or enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
12. I understand that UAC, on behalf of the participating institutions, makes offers based on the information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer.
13. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
14. I understand that all fees paid to UAC in connection with my application are not refundable under any circumstances except as required by law.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
UAC collects personal information and, in some circumstances, information regarding your health, or information about someone other than yourself, for the purpose of processing your application for postgraduate admission to tertiary institutions.
If you are providing personal information about someone other than yourself, you should tell them about UAC's Privacy Policy.
While your personal information is generally collected from you, UAC also collects information about you from other educational institutions that you have attended. UAC provides your personal information and, where applicable, your health information, to all institutions participating in postgraduate admissions through UAC. If you do not provide personal information where required in your application, UAC will not be able to process your application. Contact UAC's Privacy Officer if you have any queries.
You are able to gain access to any personal information and health information that is held about you by UAC. To obtain access, or if you have any questions, write to:
The Managing Director, UAC, Locked Bag 112, Silverwater NSW 2128.
For more information, read UAC's Privacy Policy.
Schools Recommendation Schemes declaration
Your application cannot be considered unless you accept all conditions set out below.
UAC collects information about you, including information you provide in this application, to assist in the assessment of your application. This information may be used as described below.
1. I declare that I have read and understand the questions and that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understand the UAC Privacy Policy.
3. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
4. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all institutions participating in Schools Recommendation Schemes through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions or their affiliates.
5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia, Universities Australia member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
7. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an application or enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
8. I understand that UAC, on behalf of the participating institutions, makes offers based on the information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer.
9. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
Equity Scholarships declaration
1. I declare that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understood the UAC Privacy Policy.
3. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
4. I authorise:
UAC to use Centrelink Confirmation eServices to perform a Centrelink enquiry of my Centrelink Customer details and concession card status in order to enable UAC to determine if I qualify for Equity Scholarshipsthe Australian Government Department of Human Services (the department) to provide the results of that enquiry to UAC.I understand:
The department will disclose personal information to UAC, including my name, address, concession card status, payment type, payment status, one-off payment, income, assets, deductions, shared care arrangements, partner status, Youth Allowance Independence rate, to confirm my eligibility for relevant Equity Scholarships.This consent, once signed, remains valid while I am an applicant of UAC unless I withdraw it by contacting UAC or the department.I can obtain proof of my circumstances/details from the department and provide it to UAC so that my eligibility for Equity Scholarships can be determined.If I withdraw my consent or do not alternatively provide proof of my circumstances/details, I may not be eligible for Equity Scholarships provided through UAC.5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all institutions participating in Equity Scholarships through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with this application.
7. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia (UA), UA member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
8. I understand that UAC may disclose the personal information I have given in this application to the Department of Social Services, or its successor, for the purposes of administering Relocation Scholarships and Student Start up Loans.
9. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an Equity Scholarships application and/or application for admission or an enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
10. I understand that institutions make Equity Scholarship offers based on the information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer.
11. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
Educational Access Schemes declaration
1. I declare that all the information submitted is true and complete.
2. I declare that I have read and understood the UAC Privacy Policy.
3. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
4. I authorise:
UAC to use Centrelink Confirmation eServices to perform a Centrelink enquiry of my Centrelink Customer details and concession card status in order to enable the business to determine if I qualify for a concession, rebate or servicethe Australian Government Department of Human Services (the department) to provide the results of that enquiry to UAC.I understand:
The department will disclose personal information to UAC, including my name, address, concession card status, payment type, payment status, one-off payment, income, assets, deductions, shared care arrangements, partner status, Youth Allowance Independence rate, to confirm my eligibility for Educational Access Schemes.This consent, once signed, remains valid while I am an applicant of UAC unless I withdraw it by contacting UAC or the department.I can get proof of my circumstances/details from the department and provide it to UAC so that my eligibility for Educational Access Schemes can be determined.If I withdraw my consent or do not alternatively provide proof of my circumstances/details, I may not be eligible for Educational Access Schemes provided through UAC.5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in relation to this application to all institutions participating in Educational Access Schemes through UAC or their affiliates for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions or their affiliates.
7. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia (UA), UA member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary	educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC	reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
8. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions have the right to vary or cancel an Educational Access Schemes application and/or application for admission or an enrolment made on the basis of what UAC or a participating institution determines to be untrue or incomplete information from any source.
9. I understand that institutions make offers of admission based on the consideration of Educational Access Schemes applications, which includes information provided by me and on advice received from UAC. If a participating institution subsequently finds that the information or advice was incorrect, it may withdraw the offer of admission.
10. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
Qualifications Assessment Service declaration
1. I understand that the Qualifications Assessment Statement issued to me is based on the information available to UAC as at the date of issue and that the actual assessment of my qualification/s in any future application is subject to change of confidential common assessment procedures and guidelines approved by UAC's participating institutions.
2. I declare that all information provided in this application and in documents submitted is true and correct.
3. I declare that I have read and understood the terms and conditions set out in the disclaimer.
4. I give consent for UAC to use this information for any future application made by me.
5. I understand that UAC and the participating institutions may check my visa and residency status using Visa Entitlement Verification Online (VEVO), and I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to do so.
6. I authorise UAC to verify any information provided by me.
7. I authorise UAC to provide all information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application to all participating institutions for any purpose connected with my possible selection, admission and/or enrolment in any course at any of those institutions.
8. I authorise UAC and the participating institutions to obtain available official records from any educational institution attended by me. I understand that UAC is not responsible if any institution does not provide these records.
9. I authorise UAC to collect, receive, store, transfer and use any information provided by me, or any information obtained in connection with this application, and to disclose such information to all participating institutions, Universities Australia, Universities Australia member institutions, the members of the Australasian Conference of Tertiary Admissions Centres (ACTAC), the Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Authority (TEQSA), the Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), state and territory governments and any other authority or tertiary educational institution, either in Australia or overseas, where UAC reasonably considers it is necessary to make such disclosure.
10. I understand that UAC may decline to assess my qualification/s if information required for a valid assessment is not available to UAC.
11. I understand that information and documents provided with and/or obtained in connection with this application may be used by UAC for training and research purposes and that I must notify UAC in writing within 7 days of applying if I do not wish this information to be used.
12. I understand that all fees paid to UAC are not refundable under any circumstance, except as required by law.
